<archimate:ApplicationInterface
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="'Forward' STO Interface; Vestas SAP --> DB Schenker SAP"
    id="id-e7bf641fcc984f8d8c2c65b08e4e7bfb"
    documentation="Sending Container + Additional Tool to site&#xD;&#xA;SBU/Hub Purchaser in Vestas Services GmbH creates a stock transport order (CC STO) selecting ​the material ### (Container material number). The issuing storage location is the main warehouse and the ​ receiving plant is the BU and the storage location is always 2000. The account assignment on this CC STO​ must always be Q. The STO is interfaces to Schenker using the IDoc ORDERS05.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Container Location fill-up STO&#xD;&#xA;Vestas Services GmbH creates a stock transport order (STO) where the issuing storage location is the main​warehouse and the receiving storage location is a “Rental container” storage location. The STO is interfaced​ to Schenker using the IDoc ORDERS05.&#xD;&#xA; - The materials are moved physically from the Main stock to the Rental container. ​&#xD;&#xA; - Schenker is receiving the materials at the storage location 7###. This information is interfaced to Vestas​ using the IDoc MBGMCR0&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Generic steps after STO creation:&#xD;&#xA;- When Schenker has picked the materials they make a post goods issue. This is interfaced to Vestas using ​IDoc DELVRY03 including information regarding batches and serial numbers if the materials need this ​ information (Includes the qualifier PGI). ​&#xD;&#xA;- During the GI confirmation all serial No. relevant items should be consolidated by Schenker: Schenker​ activated Batch Management for the SN relevant items (1SN = 1 Batch-No.).  Because of batch split on ​Schenker side the consolidation is necessary.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Link to Documentation;&#xD;&#xA;https://vestas.sharepoint.com/:p:/r/sites/OneTool-T153PLrollout/Shared%20Documents/T15%203PL%20rollout/00%20Requirements%20and%20Process/Vestas%20-%20DB%20Schenker%20Interface.pptx?d=w8ae74256aee84e64a3c4764fa3b4d8bb&amp;csf=1&amp;web=1&amp;e=PhplWf"/>
